<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">

<!-- Jobs -->
<jobname.captain>Mutated Mantis</jobname.captain>
<jobdescription.captain>Member of the Monsters team, kill all humans. You have 1500 vitality and slowly and passively regen, but can gain lots of HP by feasting on corpses. You attack each 2 seconds, dealing 45 blunt trauma and 5 bleeding. On land, you move slightly slower than a human, but on water you're quick and nimble. You can open regular doors, use trams and rapidly break secure doors.</jobdescription.captain>
<jobname.engineer>Researcher</jobname.engineer>
<jobdescription.engineer>Civilian Member of the Nexpharma team, escape the facility and collaborate with the MERCS and Guards. A low-level researcher, equipped with your research and your staff keycard (Admin Tier 1).</jobdescription.engineer>
<jobname.mechanic>Mechanic</jobname.mechanic>
<jobdescription.mechanic>Civilian Member of the Nexpharma team, escape the facility and collaborate with the MERCS and Guards. Basic maintenance personnel, equipped with maintancen supplies and your staff keycard (Admin Tier 1).</jobdescription.mechanic>
<jobname.securityofficer>Enforcer</jobname.securityofficer>
<jobdescription.securityofficer>Armed Member of the Nexpharma team, kill monster and inmates, but help staff to escape. On-site security personnel only meant to keep the inmates in check, equipped with a sidearm, body armor and a guard keycard (Admin Tier 1 and Weapon Tier 1).</jobdescription.securityofficer>
<jobname.medicaldoctor>Mutated Crawler</jobname.medicaldoctor>
<jobdescription.medicaldoctor>Member of the Monsters team, kill all humans. You have 1000 vitality and passively regen, but can gain lots of HP by feasting on corpses. You attack each 1 seconds, dealing around 30 bite wounds and 20 bleeding. On land, you move almost as fast as a human, and on water even more so. You can open regular doors, use trams and slowly break secure doors.</jobdescription.medicaldoctor>
<jobname.assistant>Inmate</jobname.assistant>
<jobdescription.assistant>Civilian Member of the Terrorist team, escape the facility and collaborate with the Terrorists. Subjucated, tested on and treated like scum - tonight we escape brothers! Equipped with some contraband.</jobdescription.assistant>

</infotexts>