<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">

<!-- Jobs -->
<jobname.mutatedmantis>Mutated Mantis</jobname.mutatedmantis>
<jobdescription.mutatedmantis>Member of the Monsters team, kill all humans. You have 1800 vitality and slowly and passively regen, but can gain lots of HP by feasting on corpses. You attack each 1.5 seconds, dealing 45 blunt trauma and 5 bleeding. On land, you move slightly slower than a human, but on water, you're quick and nimble. You can open regular doors, use trams and rapidly break secure doors.</jobdescription.mutatedmantis>
<jobname.researcher>Researcher</jobname.researcher>
<jobdescription.researcher>Civilian Member of the Nexpharma team, escape the facility and collaborate with the MERCS and Guards. A low-level researcher, equipped with your research and your staff keycard (Admin Tier 1).</jobdescription.researcher>
<jobname.repairmen>Repairmen</jobname.repairmen>
<jobdescription.repairmen>Civilian Member of the Nexpharma team, escape the facility and collaborate with the MERCS and Guards. Basic maintenance personnel, equipped with maintancen supplies and your staff keycard (Admin Tier 1).</jobdescription.repairmen>
<jobname.enforcerguard>Enforcer</jobname.enforcerguard>
<jobdescription.enforcerguard>Armed Member of the Nexpharma team, kill monsters and inmates, but help staff to escape. On-site security personnel only meant to keep the inmates in check, equipped with a sidearm, body armor and a guard keycard (Admin Tier 1 and Weapon Tier 1).</jobdescription.enforcerguard>
<jobname.mutatedcrawler>Mutated Crawler</jobname.mutatedcrawler>
<jobdescription.mutatedcrawler>Member of the Monsters team, kill all humans. You have 1200 vitality and passively regen, but can gain lots of HP by feasting on corpses. You attack each 1.5 seconds, dealing around 55 bite wounds and 15 bleeding. On land, you move as fast as a human, and on water, you're quick and nimble. You can open regular doors, use trams and slowly break secure doors.</jobdescription.mutatedcrawler>
<jobname.inmate>Inmate</jobname.inmate>
<jobdescription.inmate>Civilian Member of the Terrorist team, escape the facility and collaborate with the Terrorists. Subjucated, tested on and treated like scum - tonight we escape brothers! Equipped with some contraband.</jobdescription.inmate>
<jobname.jet>JET</jobname.jet>
<jobdescription.jet>Militant Member of the Terrorist team, kill monsters and nexpharma personnel, but help inmates escape. Jovian Elite Troops, give them hell!</jobdescription.jet>
<jobname.mercs>MERCS</jobname.mercs>
<jobdescription.mercs>Militant Member of the Nexpharma team, kill monsters and terrorists, but help staff escape. Mobile Emergency Rescue and Combat Squad reporting for duty!</jobdescription.mercs>

</infotexts>