<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<infotexts language="English" nowhitespace="false" translatedname="English">

<!-- Jobs -->
<jobname.captain>Mutated Mantis</jobname.captain>
<jobdescription.captain>Member of the Monsters team, kill all humans. You have 1800 vitality and slowly and passively regen, but can gain lots of HP by feasting on corpses. You attack each 1.5 seconds, dealing a bit over 30 damage. On land, you move as fast a human, but on water you're quick and nimble. You can open shaft doors and use Tram 512.</jobdescription.captain>
<jobname.engineer>Researcher</jobname.engineer>
<jobdescription.engineer>Civilian Member of the Nexpharma team, escape the facility and collaborate with the MERCS and Guards. A low-level researcher, equipped with an O2 mask, a few meds and your staff keycard (Admin Tier 1).</jobdescription.engineer>
<jobname.mechanic>Mechanic</jobname.mechanic>
<jobdescription.mechanic>Civilian Member of the Nexpharma team, escape the facility and collaborate with the MERCS and Guards. Basic maintenance personnel, equipped with a welding mask, a few tools and your staff keycard (Admin Tier 1).</jobdescription.mechanic>
<jobname.securityofficer>Enforcer</jobname.securityofficer>
<jobdescription.securityofficer>Armed Member of the Nexpharma team, kill monster and inmates, but help staff to escape. On-site security personnel only meant to keep the inmates in check, equipped with a revolver, body armor and a guard keycard (Admin Tier 1 and Weapon Tier 1).</jobdescription.securityofficer>
<jobname.medicaldoctor>Mutated Crawler</jobname.medicaldoctor>
<jobdescription.medicaldoctor>Member of the Monsters team, kill all humans. You have 1200 vitality and passively regen, but can gain lots of HP by feasting on corpses.You attack each 1.5 seconds, dealing a bit over 60 damage. On land, you move are faster a human, and on water even more so. You can open shaft doors and use Tram 512.</jobdescription.medicaldoctor>
<jobname.assistant>Inmate</jobname.assistant>
<jobdescription.assistant>Civilian Member of the Terrorist team, escape the facility and collaborate with the Terrorists. Subjucated, tested on and treated like scum - tonight we escape brothers! Equipped with a shiv and sum of dat fent.</jobdescription.assistant>

</infotexts>